Guide to the Kevin Kennedy Ephemera and Photographs AIA.063
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Photographs and Photo Negatives, 1916-2008 (inclusive); 1977-2008 (bulk); 21.67 Linear Feet in 20 record cartons
  - Co. Donegal Assoc Armory, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Co. Donegal, Co. Monaghan, AIMS Madda, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Co. Galway, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Co. Galway Institute, St. Patricks Dinner Dance, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Co. Kilkenny Dinner Dance, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Co. Leitrim, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Co. Limrick, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Co. Limerick, Barvey McGuigger, Belfast, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Co. Limrick, Co. Leitrim, Co. Roscommon, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Co. Longford, 1993-1997 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Co. Longford, Co. Leitrim, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Co. Louth, 1982-1996 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Co. Louth Assoc., Golden Pheasant, Co. Cavan, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Co. Louth Dance, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Co. Louth Dinner Dance, 1983-1991 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Co. Louth Football Dance Gaelic Park, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Co. Louth, Co. Galway, St. Patrick's Cathedral, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Co. Louth & Mineola, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Co. Monaghan Football, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Co. Monaghan Football Club, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Co. Mayo, 1985-2006 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Co. Mayo Bellendene Wheelchair, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Co. Mayo, Co. Leitrim, Tipp Crystal, 1972, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Co. Mayo Crystal Palace, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Co. Mayo, G. Park, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Co. Offally, 1985, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Co. Offally Dinner Dance, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Co. Offally Dinner, Pat Burksband, GMA Party, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Co. Offally, Frank Glynn, B of Reagan American Legion, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Co. Offally and Paul O'De Offices, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Co. Roscommon, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Co. Roscommon, Mineola, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Co. Roscommon Society, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Co. Sligo, 1991-1992, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Co. Sligo, Lewards, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Co. Sligo, St. Patricks, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Co. Tipperary, 1987-1991 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Co. Tipperary Assn, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Co. Tipperary Assoc., Installation, the Camogie Team, Buddy Mulligan's Bar, Queens, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Co. Tipperary, Astoria Manor, Dublin, Primmamski Houghey, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Co. Tipperary, Co. Sligo, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Co. Tipperary Dance, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Co. Tipperary Hurling Dance (Singer Dan O'Donnoll), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Co. Tipp, Hurlers Dance, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Co. Tipperary, New Jersey, Sheraton Center Hotel, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Co. Tyrone, Paddy Reilly, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Co. Wexford, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Cody McCane, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Cody McCane, M.H. Club, Gov Como, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Cody McCane, St. Patrick's, Paul O'Dwyer, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Columbus Parade, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Communion & Kennedys, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Con Edison Emerald, Bro. David, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Coney Island, 1989-2001 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Coney Island, M. Tierney Sidewalk, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Confirmation St. Josephs, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Confirmation St. Joseph's Church, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Confirmation St. Joseph, Camogie FR Harrison, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Congressman Joe Kennedy, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Conn Golf, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Consulate, 2004-2008 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Consulate Knork, undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Cooke Dinner & Mike Flannerys, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cooke Mass, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Cooke Mass, K of C, St. Patricks, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cork, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Cork & Galway, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Cork Hall, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Cork, Wicklow, Galway, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Council General Office, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Crystal Palace Astoria, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
  - Crystal Palace Astoria FR Colm, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Crystal Palace, Brooklyn Cody McCane, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Dan Kelly, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Dan Kelly House, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Danny Moloney, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Defea of Dream, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Dinkins, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Dinner, Yonkers, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Div 3 A.O.H., 1995 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Div 3 A.O.H., Marathon, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Div 3 & 29 A.O.H., undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Div 3 L.A.O.H., 1996 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Div 4, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Div 4 A.O.H., 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Div 4 Breckford, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Div 4 & Co. Board A.O.H., undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Division 5 A.O.H. Men Paul O'Dwyer Division, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Div 29 A.O.H., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Donegal, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Doonwoody Feis, Cattle Hill Harbor, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Doors of Hope, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Dublin, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Dulbin Dance, Mayo, Teddy Gleason, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Dublin Party, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Dunmore, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Dunmore Carnival, Fessh in Domweddy, Yonkers 3rd Ave Block Party, K & C Communion Breakfast, Coffee Shop, St. Stephens, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Dunmore Co. Galway, 1981-2003 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Dunmore Co. Galway, Brooklyn NY, St. Thomas More, Mayo, Joyce, NJ, McGowans, Kennedy, 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Dunmore Co. Galway, Galway Dinner Dance, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Dunmore Dance, Cardinal Cook's Funeral, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Dunmore & Galway, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Durrows, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Durrows, AOH Co. Board, Gaelic Park, Dunmore, K of C Charity Ball, 1982-1983, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Durrows N.Y.C. Benefit A.O.H., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Durrows Parade, undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Durrows, Tuppy Dance, City Hall, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Easter Sunday, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Easter Sunday G-Park, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Easter Sunday, Tara Gift Shop, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Ed Koch, undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Emerald Bus Lines, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Emerald Dance, Great Neck, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Emerald Golf, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Emerald Society, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Emerald Society, Cardinal Ofiaich, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Emerald Society, Co. Louth Dinner Dance, City Hall, Mayor Koch, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Emerald Society Dept of Cor., 1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Empire State Building Harbour Lights, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Farrells, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Farrells Cars, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Farrells, McManus, Woodside, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Father Bart Daly, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Father Kelly, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Father Skyler (?), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Feis, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Feish, 1983-2007 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Fesh, Dunwoody, U.I.C. Assoc, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Fesh, Harry & Margie, Archbishop Cunman, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Fesh St. John's, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Festival NJ, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Fitzpatricks Local 608, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Football, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Football Dance, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Football P.T.A.A./A.O.H., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Fort Skyler, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Fr. Bart Daly, Yonkers, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Fr. Campbell, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Fr. Colin Campbell, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Fr. Harrison Mayo, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Fr. Maurice Burke Dinner, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Frank Byrne, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Frank Byrne, Emerald Dance, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Frankie Byrne, Dunmore Co. Galway, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Frank Durkan, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Frank McGann, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Frindly Sons Grand Stand, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - From Corry Jeneuse Office, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Ft Skyler, Connoughtons, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Furniture in Basement Ireland, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - G.A.A., 1992-1995 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - G.A.A. Dinner Dance, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - G.A.A. Dinner & Wedding, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - G.A.A., Paddy Hogan, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - G.A.A., Terry, PTAA, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - G.A.A., U.I.C., 1995 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - G.A.A., U.I.C. Assoc, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Gaelic Park, 1980-2008 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Gaelic Park, Co. Board AOH, St. Thomas More Chorus, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Gaelic Park, Co. Clare, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Gaelic Park, Fr. Sean Harrigan, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Gaelic Park & G.A.A., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Gaelic Park, Gaelic Park Wedding, Wedding, Wedding & Dunwoody, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Gaelic Park, Irish Day Downtown, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Gaelic Park, K of C, NJ Galway Moss, Nellie Sullivan Dance, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Gaelic Park, Mayo, PTAA, K of C, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Gaelic Park, Sally Markher, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Gaelic Park (1916), SMA Fathers NJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Galway, 1986-2008 (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
  - Galway Assoc., 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Galway Breakfast, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Galway City, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Galway Communion Breakfast, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Galway, Communion Mass, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Galway Confirmation, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Galway D.D., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Galway Dance, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Galway Dinner Dance, Parade, Co. Louth, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Galway Dinner Dance, West Meath Dance, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Galway, Dublin, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Galway Hurlers, 1981-1983, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Galway Hurlers Dance, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Galway Hurlers and Nuns New Jersey, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Galway Hurlers, St. Thomas More, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Galway Hurling, Brooklyn Camogie, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Galway, Graig, Dunmore, Jerusalem, Ennis, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Galway Ireland, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Galway, Longford, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Galway Mass at Our Mary Breakfast, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Galway Meeting John, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Galway Offally, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Galway, Rory Dolan, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Galway & Roscommon, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Galway, Sligo, Tipperary, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Galway, U.I.C., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Garden City Bank of Ireland, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - G.C.V.E.S. Club & St. Patrick, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Gerry Adams, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Gerry Adams, Carl McCall, Paul O'D, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Gius Keenes, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Glenn Patrick Water, Tim Harnett, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - GMA, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - GMA Dinner, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - GMA Dinner Dance, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - GMA Denne Dave, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - GNA (?) Downstairs, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Golden Pheasant, Galway Dinner Dance, Co. Tippery, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Golf, 1994-2007 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Golf & Dinken (B&W), undated (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Golf, Dinner Ted Kennedy, Div 4, AIO, Hogan, Brooklyn, GP, GAA Dunmore, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Golf, Div 3, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Golf, Div 4, Emerald Dance Lombard, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Golf, Fitz, P.J.K., 1950-1955 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Golf, Roscommon, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Gormly Wedding, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Gov. Como, Mayor Koch, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Gov. George Pataki, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Gov. Mayor Terence Smith, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Gov. Pataki, Brian O'Dwyer, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Gov. Pataki, Harbour Lights, Bronx McGoldricks, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - G.P., 1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - G. Park, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Gramae Hotel Shiela McKenna, St. Joseph's Church, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Gramercy Park Hotel (?), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Grand Council, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Grand Council Emerald, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - The Grand Council Emerald Soc, St. Patrick, Bishop Henry Munsell, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Grand Marshall, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Grand Marshall, Park Ave 48th St, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Grand Stand, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Green Isle, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Grogans, 1987, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Grogans Fitzgerald Farrells, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Grogans & Mackles, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Grogan's Wedding, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Grogans Wedding & Cardinal Cook, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Grooh, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Harbour Lights, Brehan Law Society, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Harvey, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Holy Communion, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Holy Communion, IRA Parade, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Holy Cross, 1995, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Holy Cross Church, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Holy Cross Church, AOH St. Thomas More, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Holy Family, Prime Minister Charles Haughey, St. Thomas More, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Holy Trinity, Rosie O'Grady, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Hour Children, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Howley Wedding, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Howley Wedding, Gaelic Park, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Hugh C, undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - I.A.B.S., 2006 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - I.N.A., 1991 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Ins K. Morressy, undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Installation, G. Marshall, Billy Flynn, ACAB, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Ireland, 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Ireland Galway Logos P. Hopkins, undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Ireland House, 1 Fifth Ave, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Irish Consulate, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Irish Consulate Patrick & Kerry Kennedy, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Irish Consulate, Sheridan Center, West Hempstead, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Irish Council General Office Dunmore, Gal, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Irish Echo, Galway Breakfast Kathleen Murray, Gaelic Park Mill Hill Fathers A.O.H., 1986 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Irish Institute Meeting, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Irish Hall of Fame, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Irish NYPD Boxing, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Irish Parade, Feish Downwoody, Yonkers, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Irish People, Irish Pavilion, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Irish Police Gov Pataki, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Irish President, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Irish President Robson, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Irish Prime Minister, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Irish Solidarity, PTAA, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Irish Teamsters Association, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Irish Tourist Office, Gaelic Park, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Irish & US Police, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Irish Vigal, Cavan Dance, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Irish Voice, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Irish Voice, Sky Club, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Irvington Kennedys Party, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Irvington NY, K of C, Tree Trow Ball, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Isreal, South Dakota, 1984, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - I.T. Unia, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - James Joyce Awards, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Jeff Clarey, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Jeff Cleary, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Jerry Adams, 1994, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Jerry Wright, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Jerusalem, Ireland, France, Italy, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Jim Barker, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Jimmy Cagney Day, Galway Hurlers, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Joe Doherty, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Joe E. Lewis, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - John Concannon, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - John Fitzgerald House, Pioneer Dance, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - John Kelly FR Pat Morris, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - John Lowe, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - John McEnore, Sr., Tom Kennedy, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - John Reardon, GAA, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Kathleen Brennan, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Kathleen Brennan, Conway Bar, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Kay Kelly, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - K of C, 1983-2007 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - K of C, Allied Irish Bank, Dunmore Dance, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - K of C Ball Calvery Century, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - K of C Ball, U.I.C., 1997 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - K of C, Bank of Ireland, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - K of C, Bank of Ireland, St. Brendans, Dublin, Feis, Yonkers, Dunmore, UIC, Various, 1982, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - K of C Charity Ball, St. Regis Hotel, Gov. B. Byrne, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - K of C, Church Ball, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - K of C, PA, INA, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - K of C Parade B. 29, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - K of C, Paul Higgins, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - K of C Queens, undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - K of C, Solidarity Day, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - K of C St. Patrick, Co. Clare Hurling Proof, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Kelly Ryan, Easter Sunday, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Kennedy, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Kennedys Irvington, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Kerry, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Kerry Dance, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Kerry Dance Parade, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Kerry Dav Co. Gaelic Park Manor, undated (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Kerry Dinner Dance, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Kerry, Div 3 AOH, undated (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Kerry Football, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Kerry Football Dinner, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Kerry Football Dinner Dance, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kevin Kennedy's House, Mike Maloney, Friends, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kilkenny, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kilkenny B&W, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Lake George, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - L.A.O.H. & A.O.H., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - L.A.O.H. Dinner, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - [illegible] L.L., 1997 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Lehman College Bronx, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Leman College, Sr. Mooney's Irish Fair, Coney Island, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Leon Ruby, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Liam Reilly, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Limerick Dinner Dance, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Limrick Hurling Dinner, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Limrick K of C, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Limrick Tower View Center, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Local 608, Cody McCane, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Local 608 Union, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Longford, 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Longford Club, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Longford & Parade inside Cathedral Ave, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Louis Vells, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Louth, K of C, Fr. McCabe, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Lynch Wedding, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - M. Feely, Galway, Co Louth, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - M.H. Club, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - M. Healy, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - M. Keane, Minor Board, Football, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - M. Kearns, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - M. Lynch, Brooklyn, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Madison Sqaure Garden, Grogan Police, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Maloney Wedding, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Manhan, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Manhattan, Gaelic Park, Wedding, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Manhattan Club, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Manahttan Club, Brehon Law Society, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Manhattan Club, Tara Circle B&W, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Manton, Cor. Dept Jack Clark, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Marriot Hotel, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Martin Kearns, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Mary Higgins, His Eminence Ti Moran, undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Mary Joyce, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Mass, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - May & Tipperance, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Mayo, 1983, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Mayo Band, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Mayo Dinner Dance, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Mayo Football Dinner, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Mayo Mass, Durrows, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Mayo Football, Gaelic Park Bronx, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Mayo March, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Mayo, Rory Dolan, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Mayo, Roscommons, undated (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Mayo Society of New York, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Mayo, UIC, Tippa, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Mayo, UK Dinner Dance, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Mayor Giuliani, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - McGees Pub, undated (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - McGowan, Galway, Golf, Brooklyn, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - McGowans, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Michael Flannery Parade, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Mike Flannery, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Mike Kang, Van Cortland Park, Al Burke, U.I.C., 1991 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Mike Keane, Frank Carrell, Co Cavan, Branford, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Mike Kellog, Wexford, NYC, Brooklyn, Kelly Ryan, 1011 First Ave, PTAA, St. Patricks, Hour Children, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Mike McGinely Woodside, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Mike Moffat Party, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Mike Ridge, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Mineola, 1987-1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Mineola, Brooklyn, K of C, Tipperary (all B&W), undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Mineola, Cole B&W, Dublin, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Mineola, Easter Monday, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Minor Board, 1993-1998 (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
  - Minor Board, Co. Mayo, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Minor Board Football, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Minor Board Football Oliver O'Donn, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Minor Board Football Yonkers, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Minor Board G.A.A., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Minor Board, Pope, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Minor Board, St. Patrick's Cathedral, I.N.A., 1993 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Model Farm Road, Cork, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Moffett, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Monaghan Football, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Monty, Liam, & Eugene, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Moyles Christening, AOH Breakfast, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Mrs. O'Connor, Galway House, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - My Vacation, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - New Jersey, 1986-2004 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - New Jersey Pioneers, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Guild 7th Floor, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - New Year, Untitled, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - New York Camogie, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - New York Co. Board, AOH, Durrows, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - NJ Army, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Nogo Marta, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - NORAID, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - NORAID Dinner, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Nuns NJ, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Nutley New Jersey, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - NY & Brooklyn Parade, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - NY Camogie Club, Pioneers Dance, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - N.Y. Co. Board Football, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - N.Y. County Board Football Minor, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - N.Y. Ladies G.A.A., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - NY Lawyer's Assoc., Co. Tipperary, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - NY Minor Board, Co. Leitrim, Co. Monaghan, Co. Donegal, AIMs, AOH Dinner, Frank Byrne, PTAA, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - NY Minor Board & FR Skyler, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - N.Y. Minor Board Football, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Offally, 1988-1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Offally Dance, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)